const myQuestions = [
{	
	question: "What House was Harry Potter sorted into?", 
	answer: "Gryffindor",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{	
	question "Who is Harry Potter's Slytherin enemy?",
	answer: "Draco Malfoy",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1"
},
{
	question: "What is the name of Harry's owl?",
	answer: "Hedwig",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "Where does Harry sleep at his Aunt and Uncle's house in the first book?",
	answer: "under the stairs",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{ 	
	question: "Who killed Harry Potter's parents?",
	answer: "Voldemort",
	difficulty: 1
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{ 
	question: "What color is the Weasley's hair?",
	answer: "red",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "What does the Wizarding World refer to humans by?",
	answer: "Muggles",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "Which animal delivers mail?",
	answer: "owl",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "What is the Wizarding bank called?",
	answer: "Gringotts",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "What creatures run the Wizarding bank?",
	answer: "goblins",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1", 
},
{
	question: "Who doese Harry Potter marry?",
	answer: "Ginny Weasley",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "What was the name of the house elf that Harry set free?",
	answer: "Dobby",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "What object decides what House students get sorted into?",
	answer: "The Sorting Hat",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "What is the official sport at Hogwarts?",
	answer: "Quidditch",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "Who did Hermione Granger marry?",
	ansewr: "Ron Weasley",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "Who wrote Harry Potter?",
	answer: "J.K. Rowling",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{ 
	question: "Who is Harry Potter's ultimate enemy?",
	answer: "Voldemort",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "What is Harry's last name?",
	answer: "Potter",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{
	question: "What do quidditch players ride?",
	answer: "broomsticks",
	difficulty: 1,
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{ 
	question: "What type of creature did Harry have to fight in the Goblet of Fire? in the first trial";
	answer: "dragon",
	difficulty: 1, 
	topic: "Hogwarts Level 1",
},
{ 
	question: "How many siblings make up the Weasley family?",
	answer: "7",
	difficulty: 2,
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
},
{
	question: "Who was the Herboligy teacher?",
	answer: "Professor Sprout",
	difficulty 2,
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
},
{	
	question: "Who resides in the first floor girls bathroom?",
	answer: "Moaning Myrtle",
	difficulty: 2,
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
},
{
	question: "What is another name for Felix Felicis?",
	answer: "Liquid Luck",
	difficulty: 2,
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
},
{
	question: "Who did Harry Potter take to the Slughorn Christmas party?",
	answer: "Luna Lovegood",
	difficulty: 2,
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
},
{
	question; "What is Voldemort's real name?",
	answer: "Tom Marvolo Riddle",
	difficulty: 2,
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
},
{
	question: "What type of creature lives off the souls of others?",
	answer: "Death Eaters",
	difficulty: 2,
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
},
{
	question: "What is the name of the famous wandmaker that the characters receive all their wands from?",
	answer: "Garrick Ollivander",
	difficulty: 2,
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
},
{
	question: "What House was Horace Slughorn in?",
	answer: "Slytherin",
	difficulty: 2, 
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
},
{
	question: "Who died in the Triwizard Maze?",
	answer: "Cedric Diggory", 
	difficulty: 2,
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
	
},
{
	question: "How many books are in the original Harry Potter series?",
	answer: "7",
	difficulty: 2,
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
},
{
	question: "How many siblings does Harry Potter have?",
	answer: "0",
	difficulty: 2,
	topic: "Chamber of Secrets Level 2",
},
{
	question: "Who guards the entrance to the Gryffindor commons?",
	answer: "The Fat Lady",
	difficlty: 3,
	topic: "Azkaban Level 3",
},
{
	question: "What does O.W.L. stand for?",
	answer: "Ordinary Wizarding Level",
	difficulty: 3,
	topic: "Azkaban Level 3",
},
{
	question: "What is the term used to describe a wizard/witch that cannot do magic?",
	answer: "Squib",
	difficulty: 3, 
	topic: "Azkaban Level 3",
},
{
	question: "Who kills Sirius Black?",
	answer: "Bellatrix Lestrange",
	difficulty: 3, 
	topic: "Azkaban Level 3",
},
{
	question: "What does one say to close the Marauder's Map and make it blank?",
	answer: "Mischief Managed",
	difficulty: 3,
	topic: "Azkaban Level 3",
},
{
	question: "What is the name of Filch's cat?"
	answer: "Mrs. Norris",
	difficulty: 3,
	topic: "Azkaban Level 3", 
},
{
	question: "What professor teaches flying lessons?",
	answer: "Madam Hooch",
	difficulty: 3, 
	topic: "Azkaban Level 3",
},
{
	question: "What is the model of the first broom Harry ever received?",
	answer: "Nimbus 2000",
	difficulty: 3,
	topic: "Azkaban Level 3",
},
{
	question: "What quidditch position does Harry Potter play?",
	answer: "Seeker",
	difficulty: 3,
	topic: "Azkaban Level 3",
},
{
	question: "How do you summon a Patronus",
	answer: "Expecto Patronum",
	difficulty: 3,
	topic: "Azkaban Level 3", 
},
{
	question: "What House is Nearly Headless Nick the ghost for?",
	answer: "Gryffindor",
	difficulty: 4,
	topic: "The Triwizard Maze Level 4",
},
{
	question: "How many Death Eaters fought at the Battle of Hogwarts?",
	answer: "23",
	difficulty: 4,
	topic: "The Triwizard Maze Level 4",
},
{
	question: "What does Sirius Black give Harry Ptter as a gift?",
	answer: "Firebolt",
	difficulty: 4,
	topic: "The Triwizard Maze Level 4",
},
{
	question: "What do Harry, Hermione, and Ron drink to transform themselves into other people?",
	answer: "Polyjuice Potion",
	difficulty: 4,
	topic: "The Triwizard Maze Level 4",
},
{
	question: "Which Hogwarts Founder did the Sorting Hat originally belong to?",
	answer: "Godrick Gryffindor",
	difficulty: 4,
	topic: "The Triwizard Maze Level 4",
},
{
	question: "What is the name of the dragon that Hagrid hatches from an egg?",
	answer: "Norbert",
	difficulty: 4,
	topic: "The Triwizard Maze Level 4", 
},
{
	question: "Who owned the Invisibility Cloak before Harry Potter?",
	answer: "James Potter",
	difficulty: 4,
	topic: "The Triwizard Maze Level 4",
},
{
	question: "Name the magical creature that can turn itself into a person's worst fear.",
	answer: "Boggart",
	difficulty: 4,
	topic: "The Triwizard Maze Level 4",
},
{
	question: "What guards Azkaban prison?",
	answer: "Dementors",
	difficulty: 5,
	topic: "Ministry of Magic Level 5", 
},
{
	question: "What did the Weasley's and Harry Potter use to get to Daigon Alley in the first Harry Potter book?",
	answer: "Floo Powder",
	difficulty: 5,
	topic: "Ministry of Magic Level 5",
},
{
	question: "What Patronus is Harry Potter?",
	answer: "Stag",
	difficulty: 5,
	topic: "Ministry of Magic Level 5",
},
{
	question: "What are Voldemort's followers called?",
	answer: "Death Eaters",
	difficulty: 5,
	topic: "Ministry of Magic Level 5",
},
{
	question: "What Wizarding World slur does Draco call Hermione?",
	answer: "Mudblood",
	difficulty: 5,
	topic: "Ministry of Magic Level 5", 
},
{
	question: "According to the book, what color are Harry's eyes?",
	answer: "green",
	difficulty: 5,
	topic: "Ministry of Magic Level 5",
},
{
	question: "Who is the Half-Blood-Prince?",
	answer: "Snape",
	difficulty: 6,
	topic: "The Tower Level 6",
},
{
	question: "What chess piece does Ron play in Wizards Chess in the Sorcerer's Stone?",
	answer: "knight",
	difficulty: 6, 
	topic: "The Tower Level 6",
},
{
	question: "What day and month is Harry Potter's birthday?",
	answer: "July 31",
	difficulty; 6,
	topic: "The Tower Level 6",
},
{
	question: "What does Snape try to teach Harry Potter at Dumbledore's request?",
	answer: "Occlumency",
	difficulty: 6,
	topic: "The Tower Level 6",
}
];




	
	
	



 

















































































































